<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>fuck-yeah on tiago.dev</title>
    <link>https://www.tiago.dev/tags/fuck-yeah/</link>
    <description>Recent content in fuck-yeah on tiago.dev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +4200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.tiago.dev/tags/fuck-yeah/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
      <title>Being a Game Dev at a game studio, one year into it!</title>
      <link>https://www.tiago.dev/posts/thoughts/one-year-as-a-game-dev/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +4200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tiago.dev/posts/thoughts/one-year-as-a-game-dev/</guid>
      <description>so! 😊😍
Today marks 1 year since I started my career as a professional gameplay engineer!
yay!
TL;DR:
12 year old Tiago would be proud! ❤️ 32 year old Tiago is loving the change and still learning every day. Who did I write this for? myself.
I am not spending a lot of energy on making sure other people will be able to understand what I wrote. This is a reflection and celebration that I want to record for future Tiago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting at Ubisoft!</title>
      <link>https://www.tiago.dev/posts/thoughts/starting-at-ubisoft/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +4200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tiago.dev/posts/thoughts/starting-at-ubisoft/</guid>
      <description>&amp;hellip; and dealing with leaving my confort zone
I left my job&amp;hellip; &amp;hellip; as a Software Engineer at Microsoft. Last week.
In a few days, I start my new job as a Gameplay Engineer at Red Storm.
Time off &amp;hellip; before next adventure!
I had one week off between job, so my wife and I went to visit family and meet our new niece.
I filled my iddle time with prepping for my new role, playing video games and I started feeling a wide set of of emotions regarding what this new chapter in my professional life would be like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My first table!</title>
      <link>https://www.tiago.dev/posts/projects/first-diy-table/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +4200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tiago.dev/posts/projects/first-diy-table/</guid>
      <description>Why did I build a table? My work desk was bending after about 1 year of working from home.
My office equipment is actually pretty heavy.
So I decided to build a table!
Why not just buy one? I like building things.
and some youtube videos claimed I could make one for under $100.
and the biggest reasons were that if I build one:
would be fun! I would learn a new skill!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perspective Wand : Experiencing Superluminal in VR</title>
      <link>https://www.tiago.dev/posts/projects/perspective-wand/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +4200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tiago.dev/posts/projects/perspective-wand/</guid>
      <description>Have you heard of Superluminal? If not, check it out!
I really enjoyed playing it : link to Superluminal on Steam
The puzzles are incredible.
It has this game mechanic that tricks your mind. Even when you understand it, it still leaves you in awe.
If you know me, you know where this is going&amp;hellip;
I wondered how would it feel to interact with this game mechanic in the real world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why do I blog?</title>
      <link>https://www.tiago.dev/posts/thoughts/why-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +4200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tiago.dev/posts/thoughts/why-blog/</guid>
      <description>Why am I starting a blog? I am creating this blog as a sort of a personal growth record keeping.
The posts I am creating are usually around the areas of:
books I am reading or listening to my endless quest of working on projects a public &amp;ldquo;fuck yeah list&amp;rdquo; Books As I read and listen to book, I take notes. Doing that really helps to critically understand what I am reading and it helps to retain knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
